virtual-secrets.com 2019-08-04

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy:

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which virtual-secrets.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [http://virtual-secrets.com](http://virtual-secrets.com/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by virtual-secrets.com.

Personal identification information

We may collect personally identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

IP Address information

IP addresses will not be displayed visibly on our site ever. (Effective 10/21/2010) Standard server logging will be used but is only accessible by the system administrator. Logging is scanned nightly by an application and any activity that is ‘red flagged’ is sent to the system administrator electronically. This ‘red flag’ activity is intrusion detection, errors and other maintenace items. Standard web use is not ever flagged.

If you would like to obtain an IP address of a poster please send your subpoena to the address on the following [website](http://www.linode.com/about/).

IP addresses of posters can be obtained in the event of a law enforcement welfare check. That means if you say you are going to kill yourself or someone then I obtain IP information accordingly and send to the ISP so they can forward to law enforcement for a welfare check. I’ve only had this happen once. Don’t make this a habit.

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. This information will never be disclosed.

Media

Ownership of  Virtual Secrets images for the weekly column “Virtual Secrets”

Ownership of all images uploaded for Virtual Secrets are property of virtual-secrets.com.

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

Web browser cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

How we use collected information

virtual-secrets.com collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

– Commenting (since all comments ‘require’ name and email address)  
– Commenting as anonymous is allowed. The post writer can determine if the comment is worth publishing.  
– virtual-secrets comments are moderated by the post writer.

What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.  
Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

Analytics

Analytics are collected through Jetpack.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

If there is an error in coding software or server side which displays email addresses and names from comment fields on virtual-secrets.com the owner is not held responsible. The owner will try to diagnose and fix the issue as soon as possible.

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

How we protect your data

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Changes to this privacy policy

virtual-secrets.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us using the [Contact form](http://virtual-secrets.com/contact).

This document was last updated on May 25, 2018

Privacy policy created by [Generate Private Policy](http://www.generateprivacypolicy.com/) and also WordPress.com
